보호자의 시청감독이
필요한 작품입니다
제작 : 권성현
(hasasawl@empal.com)
네이트 드라마 24 자유제작
(http://club.nate.com/24)
There are those who believe that a child
in her womb shares his mother's dreams.
엄마의 꿈을 뱃속의 아이와
나눌 수 있다고 믿는 이들이 있다
Her love for him.
Her hopes for his future.
아이를 향한 엄마의 사랑
아이의 미래에 대한
엄마의 희망이
엄마 안에서 아이가 자는 동안
마치 이야기하듯 전해진다고 믿는다
Is it told to him in pictures
while he sleeps inside her?
Is that why he reaches for her
in that first moment
그것이 아이가 첫 순간에
엄마에게 손을 뻗는 이유이며
엄마의 손길에
울음을 터뜨리는 이유일까?
and cries for her touch?
But what if you'd known since he was
inside you what his life held for him?
하지만 아이가 당신 뱃속에
있을 때부터
그 아이의 삶이 아이를 얽맬 것을
알게 된다면 어쩌겠는가?
그 아이가 쫓기게 된다면..
That he would be hunted.
That his fate was tied
to the fate of millions.
수백만의 사람들의 운명이
그 아이의 운명에 달려있다면..
That every moment of your life
will be spent keeping him alive.
당신 삶의 모든 순간이
그 아이를 살리기 위해 소비된다면..
Would he understand
why you were so hard?
아이는 당신이 그토록
힘들게 사는 이유를 이해해 줄까?
당신이 아이를 그토록 엄하게
다스리는 이유는?
Why you held on so tight?
Will he still reach for you
if the only dream
아이와 함께 나누는 유일한 꿈이
악몽 뿐이라면
you ever shared
with him was a nightmare?
아이는 여전히 당신에게
손을 내밀까?
아이는 내 사랑이 혈액처럼
자신에게 흐른다는 걸 알까?
Would he know my love
runs through him like blood?
John, now.
존, 나오렴
Now!
어서!
조건부배포/수정금지
배포시 제작자와 출처를 꼭 표기해 주세요
- The cops make you at the diner?
- I don't know.
경찰들이 식당에 왔어요?
모르겠다
Maybe.
아마 그럴 거야
동영상 정보
HDTV-0TV / 349MB
그래
Yes. Definitely.
확실해졌네
Sarah Connor! John Connor!
사라 코너!
존 코너!
Drop what you're carrying.
가지고 있는 걸 버리고
Put your hands on your head
머리 위에 손 올리고
바닥에 무릎 꿇어!
and kneel on the ground.
Now!
당장!
Do me a favor, will you?
좀 도와주세요, 괜찮죠?
Fix it.
치마 좀 내려줘요
총격이다, 총격이다!
경관이 당했다!
Drop your weapon!
무기 버려.. 아악!
나와!
Move!
엎드려
도망가!
You run! Run!
도망가라고!
John!
존!
John. John.
John.
John?
존, 존..
어서 해!
Do it!
어서 하라고!
Do it! Kill me! Nothing matters anymore.
날 죽여!
그럼 더이상
아무 문제 없잖아
날 죽이라고!
Kill me!
네 말이 맞다
You're right.
Nothing matters anymore.
더이상 아무 문제 없다
Only the boy.
오직 그 아이 외엔..
The future's ours.
미래는 우리 것이다
And it begins now.
이제 시작이다
바로 지금
자기
Did you scream or something?
자기가 소리쳤어?
Scream? No.
소리? 아니..
Go back to sleep.
다시 자
I can't. Got an early shift.
안 돼
일찍 교대하기로 했거든
Are you all right?
자기 괜찮아?
I'm good.
괜찮아
- Yeah?
- I'm great.
그래?
정말 괜찮아
Well, you damn well better be.
음, 자기가 흉봐도 좋아
You know, the guy down at the store
told me any woman would be lucky
있잖아, 가게에서 어떤 사람이 나한테,
이 반지를 갖는 여자는
행운이라고 하더라구
to have this ring.
He doesn't know the giver like I do.
그 사람은 나처럼 해 주는
사람을 몰라서 그래
You wanna know a secret?
비밀 하나 알고 싶어?
모르겠어
I don't know. I don't like secrets.
난 비밀 안 좋아해
No? This is a good one.
그래?
이거 재밌는 얘긴데..
- Really?
- Yeah.
- 정말?
- 그럼
All right.
좋아
John picked it out.
이거 존이 고른 거야
그래, 일정 부분은..
Sort of.
You know I'd been looking
and looking and I...
내가 계속 보고 또 봤는데,
모든 색상, 가공수준, 투명도..
kinda starting freaking myself out
with the whole color
이런 거 다 보려니까
정말 정신이 없어지더라구
and cut and clarity...
So you turned the job over
to a 15-year-old boy.
그래서 자기는 15살 소년으로
직업을 바꿨구
You think I'm a jackass, don't you?
자기가 보기에
나 바보 같지, 안 그래?
I'm thinking I love you.
내 생각엔 내가 자기를
사랑하는 것처럼 보이는데..
Always rember that.
항상 그걸 기억해 줘
Early shift.
일찍 교대한다며
가야겠네
- Better get going.
- Right.
그래
Early shift.
일찍 교대해야지
Bye.
안녕
Season 1 Episode 1
Pilot (v. 1.00)
터미네이터
사라 코너 연대기
1x01
Pilot
http://Projet-SG.net
웨스트 포크, 네브라스카주
1999년 8월 24일
레나 헤디
(사라 코너 役)
Mom, how many times have I told you
엄마, 내가 몇 번이나 말했잖아요
엄마가 그러실 때마다 소름끼친다구요
it's freaky when you do that?
미안
I'm sorry.
토마스 데커
(존 코너 役)
What's going on?
뭐하시는 거예요?
섬머 글루
(터미네이터/카메론 필립스 役)
리차드 T. 존스
(제임스 엘리슨 役)
We can't stay here, John.
우린 여기 계속 지낼 수 없다, 존
What?
뭐라구요?
It's not safe.
안전하지 않아
Not safe from who?
누구로부터 안전하지 않다는 거예요?
No one knows us.
아무도 우릴 모른다구요
No one asks questions.
It's been almost two years.
아무도 의심스러워 하지 않고
거의 2년이나 지냈어요
School starts in, like, three weeks.
3주만 있으면
학기도 시작된다구요
- We need to go.
- No, you need to go.
우리는 떠나야 해
아뇨, 엄마가 떠나야죠
You're scared. He gave you a ring
and now you're freaking out.
엄마는 두려운 거예요
아저씨가 반지를 줬는데,
엄마는 그게 불안한 거죠
I know you like him.
네가 그 사람을
좋아하는 건 알아
So do you, mom!
엄마도 그렇잖아요!
So do you. You love him, I know you do.
맞아요
엄마는 아저씨를 사랑해요
그렇다는 거 저도 안다구요
Listen to me.
The cops will never find us. We're safe.
제 말 들어보세요
경찰들은 절대로 우리 못 찾아요
우린 안전하다구요!
Don't you think that, John!
절대 그렇게 생각하지 마, 존!
Don't you ever think that. Look at me!
절대 그렇게 생각하면 안 돼
날 보렴!
No one is ever safe.
누구도 결코 안전하지 않아
Half an hour.
30분 주마
One bag.
가방은 하나만..
그리고 총들 챙겨
Plus the guns.
엄만 팬케익 만들테니..
I'll make pancakes.
모든 가족은 저마다
규칙을 가지고 있다
Every family has rules.
그리고 우리도
우리의 규칙이 있다
And we had ours.
"머리를 숙이고,"
Keep your head down,
"눈을 들어라"
keep your eyes up,
resist the urge to be seen
as important or special.
"중요하거나 특별해 보이는
충동에 저항하라"
Know your exits.
"탈출구를 알라"
그러니까, 약혼자 분이 실제로
실종된 게 아니라는 겁니다, 맞죠?
I mean, she's not
exactly missing, right?
- The way you explain it.
- Right.
선생님의 말씀에 따르면..
맞소, 내가 말한 대로,
그 사람은 실종된 게 아니라
The way I explained it,
she's not missing.
She left.
떠나버린 거요
Happens more than you think.
이런 일은 생각보다
자주 일어납니다
You don't know her.
경관님이 그 사람을
몰라서 그래요
전 선생께서도 그녀를 모른다고
말씀드리죠, 딕슨 씨
I can say the same to you, Mr. Dixon.
FBI?
Been together long?
함께 오랫동안 사셨나요?
Six months, maybe. Bit of a whirlwind.
6개월 정도된 것 같소
작은 폭풍이 일었지만요
You have no idea, the whirlwind.
선생께선 진짜 폭풍이 뭔지
전혀 모르시는군요
Tell me,
말씀해 보세요
스카이넷 방어 시스템이
당신에게 의미가 있습니까?
does the Skynet defense system
mean anything to you?
아뇨
No.
How about this guy?
이 사람은 어떤가요?
Miles Dyson.
마일즈 다이슨
No.
아뇨
Never seen him before.
전 이 사람 본 적도 없는데요
That's because he's dead.
그건 이 사람이
죽은 사람이기 때문이죠
Your fiancee, freshly escaped
from the pescadero mental hospital,
선생님의 약혼녀는,
일전에 페스카데로 정신병원을
탈출했습니다
그리고 이 사람을 폭발로 죽였죠,
2년 전에요
blew him apart two years ago.
Leveled a four story
research lab along with him.
그가 있는 4층 짜리 연구소를
날려버린 겁니다
But since there's no lethal injection
하지만 재물의 파손을 위한
어떤 치명적인 침입은 전혀 없었죠
for the destruction of property,
그냥 살인자로만 봅시다, 우리 나라
최고의 컴퓨터 과학자 중 한 사람이며..
let's just stick with the murder of
one of our county's brightest
computer scientists. And...
그리고..
dedicated family man.
가정에 충실한 한 남자를
살해했으니까요
That's... it's just not...
그건.. 그게 저..
그 사람이 왜 그랬겠어요, 네?
Why would she do that?
Well, you know, Mr. Dixon.
아, 선생께서도 아실텐데요, 딕슨 씨
It's the robots.
로봇 때문입니다
The ones from the future.
미래에서 온 것들이죠
The ones Skynet sent to kill her son.
스카이넷이 그녀의 아들을
죽이려고 보낸 것들입니다
Which makes total sense.
전혀 말이 안 되는 것 같죠
Because, in the future,
John's not only her son, but...
그게 미래에는 존이 그저 그녀의
아들이기만 한 게 아니기 때문이죠, 그런데..
What does it say here?
자, 여기 뭐라고 써 있게요
"The leader of the resistance
"온 인류를 전멸하도록 제작된"
fighting artificially
intelligent machines
"기술적으로 매우 뛰어난 기계들과"
determined to annihilate
the human race."
"싸우는 저항군의 지도자"
Did he strike you that way?
그 아이가 당신에게 그런 쪽
얘기를 한 적 있습니까?
Leader of a scrappy band of rebels?
반항아들의 쓰레기 같은
밴드의 지도자라고요?
Luke Skywalker type?
'루크 스카이워커' 같은 타입이래요?
He's just a kid.
웃기는 소리 마쇼
웃기지 말라구
그 아이는 내게 아들과 같소
He's a great kid.
He was like a son to me.
I came down here for help.
난 도움을 청하러 왔는데,
나한테 이따위 걸 물어보다니..
You can't really be asking me this!
No.
아뇨
I'm not.
물은 게 아닙니다
This is just my patter, Mr. Dixon.
이건 그냥 제가 수다 좀
떤 것 뿐이죠, 딕슨 씨
This is just me impressing upon you
이건 그저 선생께서,
자신의 삶에 찾아온 사랑이자
that I'm not here
because you lost your fiancee.
행복했던 시간의 전부였던
약혼녀를 잃어버려서
Love of your life
and all-around good time girl.
제가 여기 온 것이 아니란 걸
알려 드리려는 겁니다
I'm here because my boss,
the United States of America,
제가 여기 온 것은
저의 상관, 미합중국이
thinks Sarah Connor is a deluded...
사라 코너에 대해,
미래에 어떤 남자가 전 세계를 향해
Dangerous grade "A" whack-a-mole
who killed a man because she believes
that in the future he'll invent
전쟁을 선언할 컴퓨터 시스템을
발명한다고 믿고 그 남자를 죽인
a computer system
that declares war on the world.
최고 위험 등급의 괴물이라고 생각하기 때문입니다
So let's begin with her name.
그럼 그녀의
이름부터 시작합시다
알겠습니다,
'코너'가 아닌 거죠
I understand it's not Connor.
레드 벨리, 뉴 멕시코
1999년 9월 6일
You'll be responsible
for three chapters a week.
너희는 한 주에
세 장은 공부해야 하고
You have a quiz each friday.
매주 금요일에
쪽지시험을 보게 된다
부모님의 동의 하에
한 번의 재시험이 허락된다
You're allowed one make-up test
with a parent's note.
이름이 뭐니?
What's your name?
John.
존이야
Cameron.
난 카메론
And no talking...
그리고 내가 말할 때는
얘기하지 말아라
while I'm talking.
John?
존?
안녕
I haven't seen you around here before.
전에 이 주변에서 본 적 없는데
- Did you just move here?
- Yeah, I did.
이사왔니?
그래, 맞아
Sucks for you.
참 안됐다
우리 아빤 트랙터를 파셔
My dad sells tractors.
- What about yours?
- Insurance.
너희 아빠는?
보험하셔
Really? What kind?
정말?
어떤 종류?
The boring kind.
지겨운 종류
Those are the kind of tractors
my dad sells.
그건 우리 아빠가 파는
트랙터 종륜데..
What about your mom?
너희 엄마는 뭐하셔?
My mom stays home.
우리 엄마는 집에 계셔
You know, I really gotta get
to the next class, so...
알겠지만, 나 정말로
다음 수업 들어가야 돼, 그래서..
So...
그래서..
maybe i'll see you later?
아마도 또 볼 수 있겠지?
그럼, 물론이지
Sure, yeah.
Bye.
안녕
This is a hick town, mom.
여긴 정말 촌구석이에요, 엄마.
We've been in worse places.
더 나쁜 곳에도 있어 봤잖니
A lot worse.
훨씬 더 나쁜 곳에서도 말야
Well, my clothes are all wrong.
제 옷이 하나같이 엉망이에요
I need, like, some different shirts.
아무래도..
다른 셔츠가 필요할 거 같아요
You know, here everyone wears boots?
엄마도 아시겠지만,
여기 사람들은 전부 부츠를 신어요?
Like, cowboy boots.
카우보이 부츠 같은 걸로요
I hate cowboy boots.
카우보이 부츠는 정말 싫어요
I'll see what I can do.
엄마가 할 수 있는 일을
알아볼 거야
Their computers are like,
from the frigging '50s or something.
학교 컴퓨터들은 무슨
50년 대 물건 같아요
Their computers?
컴퓨터라고?
I thought we agreed...
난 우리가 합의한 줄 아는데..
아뇨, 아뇨, 그건 제 잘못 아녜요
It wasn't my fault
they switched my class.
그냥 우리 교실에 켜져 있었어요
I don't need you to be caught hacking.
내가 알고 싶은 건
네가 해킹을 그만두었냐는 거야
I'm not hacking, mom.
God, I know the rules.
해킹 안 했어요, 엄마
저도 규칙은 안다구요
They're, like, written on the inside
of my eyeballs, all right?
그 규칙들 눈알에 새겨놓은 것
같다구요, 됐어요?
Hey.
얘야
You meet any pretty girls?
너 예쁜 여자애들을 만난거지??
No, I'm telling you, it's a hick town.
아녜요, 말했잖아요,
촌구석이라구요
말해 봐
Come on.
Agent Ellison.
엘리슨 요원님
Welcome to New Mexico.
뉴 멕시코에 오신 걸
환영합니다
The sheriff's detachment'll hustle you
around on your business here,
보안관님께서,
요원님이 여기서 하시는 일들
착착 잘 되게 하라고
저를 보내셨어요
whatever that is, he wouldn't say.
그게 뭐든지요,
말씀은 안 하셨지만요
He doesn't know.
그 분은 모르는 일입니다
I lied to you yesterday.
나 어제 너한테 거짓말했어
My dad doesn't sell insurance.
우리 아버지 보험 안 하셔
He's dead.
돌아가셨거든
He was a soldier.
He was killed on a mission.
군인이셨고
작전 중에 돌아가셨어
I'm sorry.
미안..
뭐.. 괜찮아
It's all right. My mom was
pregnant with me when it happened.
우리 엄마는 그때 나를 임신 중이셨고, 결국 난 한 번도 아버지를 못 봤어
I never even knew him.
So it's all right.
그래도 괜찮아
My mom,
우리 엄마는..
어, 엄.. 엄마는 불안증이 좀 있으셔
she's kind of uptight.
Actually, no, she's
실제로는, 아니지, 엄마는..
정말 불안해하셔서, 방과 후에
내가 곧장 집에 오길 바라시지
really uptight.
She likes me to come home
straight after school
그래서 재치란 게 없으신 분이고,
뭐 그래, 알겠어?
and hang out with her and
that kind of thing, you know?
내가 엄마의 전부거든
I'm all she's got.
Thank you for explaining.
얘기해 줘서 고마워
It'll be our secret.
우리의 비밀로 하자
Mr. Ferguson is ill today.
퍼거슨 선생님이
오늘 아프시다
My name is Cromartie.
내 이름은 크로마티고..
그게 이름 전부예요,
마돈나처럼요?
This that your only name? Like madonna?
마돈나?
Madonna?
Why? No.
왜?
아니다
Let's take attendance, then.
출석 부르자
마리 부오이
Mary Booai.
Here.
네
도널드 체이스
Donald Chase.
Here.
네
- Franklin Lane.
- Here.
프랭클린 레인
네
Cynthia Nolan.
신시아 놀란
Here.
네
웨인 파커
Wayne Parker.
네
Here.
Cameron Phillips.
카메론 필립스
Cameron?
카메론?
Here.
여기요
Reese?
리스?
Do we have a John...
이 반에 존..
Reese?
리스가 있나?
Excellent.
그거 잘됐군
Class dismissed.
수업은 끝났다
Witnesses are reporting gunfire
just minutes ago
목격자들에 따르면,
몇 분 전, 레드 벨리에 있는
크레스트 뷰 고등학교에서
총격 사건이 있었다고 합니다
at Crestview High School in Red Valley.
Police are...
경찰은..
Come with me if you want to live.
살고 싶으면
나랑 같이 가
Sarah Connor.
사라 코너
Where is he?
What have you done with him?
내 아들 어딨지?
그 애한테 무슨 짓을 했어?
You don't know.
모르는군
너도 몰라
You don't know...
Killing yourself is the best strategy.
널 죽이는 건
최고의 전술이다
If you're alive,
I can use you against him.
하지만 네가 살아있다면
그를 잡는 데 널 이용할 수 있다
존?
- John?
- Mom, mom.
엄마, 엄마
- I tried to call you.
- Mom, I've been trying to call you.
너한테 전화했었다
저도 전화하는 중이었어요
제 말 잘 들으세요, 알겠죠?
Listen to me, okay? They're back.
그것들이 돌아왔어요
- It's back.
- John, slow down.
돌아왔다구요
존, 진정해라
- Where are you?
- I'm going to the house.
어디 있니?
집으로 가는 중이에요
나도 곧 가마
- I'll be right there.
- Mom!
엄마!
I love you, John. Stay right there.
사랑한다, 존
집에 계속 있거라
Let's go.
얼른 가자
존?
John?
John!
존!
- Are you okay?
- Mom?
- 너 괜찮니?
- 엄마?
- John?
- Mom?
- 존!
- 엄마!
존! 안 돼!
John!
No!
존!
괜찮은 함정이지?
Neat trick. You like?
맘에 들어?
Next time you do
what you're trained to do.
다음 번엔 훈련한대로 하거라!
You run. Go!
도망가
어서!
- Did you stop him?
- 120 seconds and the system reboots.
네가 저 녀석을 막은거야?
120초 후에 리부팅될 거예요
- I was sent here to protect John.
- Not now. Not yet.
난 존을 보호하기 위해 보내졌어요
지금 말고..
이따 얘기하자
You might wanna put those
back in the holster.
아무래도 그것들을 다시
권총집에 넣는 게 좋겠구나
We should be good here two more hours.
우린 여기서 두 시간은
더 가야 해
Hit the border at lunchtime.
점심 때까지 국경에
도착해야 해
What year are you from?
몇 년도에서 왔지?
2027.
2027년이요
How long have you been looking for us?
우릴 찾는 데에 얼마나 걸렸지?
73 days.
73일이요
And the war?
그럼, 전쟁은?
The Skynet missile defense system
스카이넷 미사일 방어 시스템이
2011년 4월 19일에 가동되면서
goes online april 19th, 2011.
Declares war on mankind
인류에게 전쟁을 선언하고,
and triggers a nuclear apocalypse
two days later.
이틀 후에 핵 대참사로
전쟁을 시작해요
Miles Dyson.
하지만, 마일즈 다이슨은..
Someone else builds Skynet.
어떤 사람이 스카이넷을
계속 구축하죠
Who?
누가?
- We don't know.
- You don't know who builds the computer
우리도 몰라요
세계를 멸망시킬 컴퓨터를
구축한 사람을 너희가 모른다?
- that blows up the world?
- I wasn't sent here for that.
나는 그것때문에
여기 보내진 게 아니에요
No, you were sent here to keep my son
아니겠지, 너는 내 아들이
암살되는 것을 막으려고 보내졌어
from being assassinated.
Your fiance went to the police.
당신의 약혼자가 경찰에게 갔습니다
You should have changed your alias.
당신은 성을 바꿔야 해요
Go to hell.
꺼져 버려!
They'd have found you anyway.
그들은 어떤 방법으로든
당신들을 찾아낼 겁니다
They always do.
그들은 항상 그러니까요
There's Kevlar in that chair.
저 의자는 방탄 섬유예요
APB's statewide, but it's been...
- 주 전체에 지명수배 내렸는데, 그게..
- 19시간 지났죠
19 hours.
What the hell happened here?
여기서 대체 무슨 일이
있었던 건지..
22 witnesses, Deputy Ridge.
22명의 증인,
대표는 릿지
22 of your good townfolk.
당신의 평화로운
마을 사람들 22명
That's a whole football team.
전부 미식축구 팀이죠
Guess what 19 of 'em saw?
그들 중 19명이 본 게 뭘까요?
A shooter with some kind of robot leg.
로봇 다리 같은 걸
달고 있는 저격범이요
A shooter...
로봇 다리 같은 걸
달고 있는 저격범이라..
with some kind of robot leg.
Hey.
Why is this happening again?
왜 이런 일이
또 일어나는 거죠?
I don't know.
모르겠구나
You stopped it.
엄마는 그걸 막았어요
I guess I didn't.
내가 해내지 못했단
생각이 드는구나
Well, you can.
하지만 엄마는 하실 수 있어요
You changed the future.
You just didn't change it enough.
엄마는 미래를 바꿨어요
그저 충분히 바꾸지
못했을 뿐이죠
So you can do it again.
그러니 한 번 더
하실 수 있을 거예요
- I don't know, John.
- I can't keep running.
나도 잘 모르겠구나, 존
전 계속 전력할 수 없어요
I can't.
전 해낼 수 없다구요
I'm not who they think I am.
전 그것들이 생각하는
그런 사람이 아니에요
Some messiah.
일종의 구세주 말이죠
You don't know that.
네가 몰라서 그래
I know.
전 알아요
I can't lead an army.
전 군대를 이끌 수 없어요
Maybe that's you, but it'll never be me.
아마 그건 엄마일 거예요
난 절대 아녜요
그러니 엄마가
그걸 멈춰야 해요
So you've gotta stop it.
제발요
Please.
Mom.
엄마
All right.
알겠다
All right what?
뭘 알겠어요?
I'll stop it.
내가 막으마
내가 막을 거야
We're not going across the border.
우리는 국경을
넘어가지 않을 거야
Where are we going?
그럼 어디로 가죠?
To find Skynet.
스카이넷을 찾으러 갈 거야
Chip?
과자 먹을래?
Back at school,
학교에 다시 갔을 때,
넌 나에게 거짓말한 걸 사과했어
you apologized for lying to me.
So I should apologize for lying to you.
그러니 나도 너에게
거짓말한 걸 사과해야겠어
It's all right. I get it.
괜찮아, 이해해
You needed to get close to me.
넌 나랑 가까워져야 했잖아
그러니까 그건 그저..
It's just the way you're...
programmed.
프로그램된 거니까
Like some hot girl is really gonna try
and make friends with the new weird kid.
멋진 여자애처럼 되려고 노력하고
낯선 이상한 아이와
친구가 되라 정도로 말이지
If I'd have thought about it,
내가 그걸 다 알았다면,
I would've known something
was messed up, you know?
모든 게 다 엉망이 됐을 거야, 알아?
In the future, you have many friends.
미래에, 넌 많은 친구가 생겨
What model are you?
넌 무슨 모델이야?
Are you new? You seem...
신형이야?
넌 좀..
different.
달라 보여
I am.
맞아
Let's go.
가자
로스엔젤레스, 켈리포니아주
1999년 9월 9일
다이슨의 저택
Mom, pizza's here.
엄마! 피자 왔어!
Mom, the pizza!
엄마! 피자 왔다고!
엄마!
Mom.
You.
당신!
We need to talk about Miles, Tarissa.
마일즈에 대해
얘기할 게 있어요, 테레사
Danny, go to your room. Right now.
데니, 네 방으로 가렴
어서 당장!
How dare you come here.
어떻게 당신이 감히
여길 올 수 있지?
I know what they told you,
but it didn't happen that way.
그 사람들이 뭐라고 한 지는 알아요
하지만 그렇게 된 게 아니에요
여기서 당장 꺼져
Get the hell out of here.
- Now.
- It didn't happen that way.
당장!
그게 그렇게 된 게 아니라구요
I can't let you do that.
당신이 그렇게 믿도록
둘 수는 없어요
꺼지라니까!
- Let go!
- Listen to me!
내 말 좀 들어봐요!
I didn't kill Miles.
내가 마일즈를
죽인 게 아니에요
All right, I didn't do it.
내가 한 게 아니라구요
I would never.
절대 아니에요
Miles was a hero.
마일즈가 스스로
택한 길이었어요
Then why are you here?
그러면 된 거지
여기 왜 온 거야?
We're back.
우리가 돌아왔습니다
You told me there'd be no more machines.
당신이 나한테 말했잖아
더이상 기계들은 안 생길 거라고
Look, it's happening again.
Everything we fought to stop.
그게 다시 일어났어요
우리가 막으려고
싸웠던 모든 게요
Miles' work at Cyberdyne
is the only link we have.
사이버다인에서의 마일즈의 연구만이
우리가 가진 유일한 단서예요
Is there anyone, anywhere
누구든..
어느 곳이든, 마일즈의 연구에
관심을 보인 사람 없었어요?
who's shown an interest in his work?
누구든 그가 얘기한 사람은요?
Anyone he could've told.
Someone he forgot.
마일즈가 잊어버렸을
사람이라도요
There's nobody. It's all gone.
아무도 없어
모두 사라졌다구
You destroyed it all.
당신이 전부
부숴버렸잖아
You and Miles destroyed...
당신하고 남편이
부숴버렸잖아..
You destroyed everything.
당신들이 모두
부숴버렸으면서..
We have to go.
가야 해요
Now.
당장이요!
Help me.
도와줘요
Help my son.
내 아들을 도와줘요
엄마, 엄마!
Mom! Mom!
Oh, god.
오, 세상에!
붕대랑
소독용 알콜 사 와
Bandages, rubbing alcohol.
엄마, 의사한테 보여야..
- Mom, you need a doctor.
- Go!
어서 가
We'll find cover out back.
우선 숨을 곳을
찾아야 해
First aid kit on the floor.
짐칸에 구급상자 있어
Get it done before he gets back.
그 놈이 다시 오기 전에
얼른 해 버려
I'll get some ice. It'll numb you,
얼음을 좀 가져올게요
그게 통증을 가라앉히고
출혈을 좀 늦출 수 있을 거예요
slow the blood loss.
Needle and thread
to slow the blood loss.
출혈을 늦추려면 바늘로 꼬매
Do it now.
어서 해
We can't keep running.
우리 계속 도망다니진
못할 거야
I'll lose my boy.
난 아들을 잃겠지
He'll leave me.
그 아인 나를 떠날 거야
What time is it?
지금 몇 시지?
7시 52분이요
7:52.
How you feeling?
좀 어때요?
Better.
훨씬 나아졌어
Good.
좋아요
- We need to go.
- Where?
갈 곳이 있어요
어딜?
I'll show you.
내가 안내할게요
So do you have, like, an account here?
그러니까 네가 여기
계좌 같은 걸 가지고 있어?
Safety deposit box.
안전보관함이야
When'd you open that?
언제 그걸 개설했지?
1963.
1963년이요
Everybody on the floor!
모두 바닥에 엎드리세요!
Please.
부탁합니다
Keys to the safety deposit boxes.
안전보관함 열쇠 꺼내요
Get inside. Keys.
안으로 들어가요,
열쇠 주세요
Lock us in, and then get away
from the door.
우리를 안에 넣고 잠궈요
그리고 문에서 멀리 떨어지세요
만약 그렇게 하지 않는다면
내가 알게 될 겁니다
I'll know if you don't.
You said you had a safety deposit box.
네가 안전보관함을
보유하고 있다고 했잖니
I do.
맞아요
Open these boxes.
이 함들을 열어요
Put everything you find on the table.
탁자 위에 찾은 걸
전부 올려놓으세요
Carefully.
조심스럽게요
여기요, 제임스!
Hey, James! You gotta see this.
이것 좀 보세요
The alarm tripped seven minutes ago.
7분 전에 경보가 울렸어요
Camera autodumps a digital copy
to the LAPD servers.
카메라에서 LA경찰 서버로 보내진
디지털 복사본이에요
Don't you know 'em?
저 사람들 몰라요?
Less and less all the time.
점점 더 모르겠구만
Is that from the future?
그게 미래에서 온 거야?
You can't bring anything
through when you come.
네가 올 때는 아무것도
가지고 올 수 없어
Not weapons, not clothing.
무기도, 옷도,
어떤 것도 안 돼
Nothing.
You send someone back to build it.
네가 누군가를 돌려보내,
이걸 만들게 하려고
What is it?
그게 뭔데?
Hope.
희망
위협요소
없음
Is that the police?
경찰인가?
No. Get away from the door.
아니
문에서 떨어져
Why?
왜?
그게 이유야
That's why.
That better be what I think it is.
그게 내가 생각하는
물건이었으면 좋겠는데..
One of our best engineers.
우리의 최고 엔지니어들 중 한 명이
Took him eight months
to scavenge the parts.
각 부품들을 끌어모으는 데에
8개월이 걸렸어요
동위원소 용해제가 빨간 색이 되면
그때 쏘세요
When the isotope solution
turns red, then fire.
Isotope?
동위원소..?
Is this nuclear?
이거 핵 무기야?
아뇨, 꼭 그런 건 아니에요
No, not really.
우리를 안에 넣고 가두라고 한
이유는 모르겠지만,
I still don't get why you locked us in.
We didn't have to get trapped like rats.
우리가 쥐처럼 덫에 걸릴
필요는 없다고 보는데..
덫에 걸린 거 아냐
We're not trapped.
What is that?
그게 뭐지?
The engineer got a job
building the vault
엔지니어는 이 전송장치
만드는 일도 했어요
그래서 우리는 항상 집으로
돌아갈 수 있었죠
so we'd always have a way back home.
What have you done?
넌 뭘하고 있지?
You wanna find Skynet?
스카이넷을 찾길 원해요?
You wanna stop Skynet?
스카이넷을 막길 원해요?
- This is the way.
- You don't know who builds it!
이게 그 방법이에요
넌 누가 그걸 구축했는지 모르잖아
몰라요, 하지만 우리는 그게 어디에,
언제 세워지는지는 알죠
No, but we know where and we know when.
We can go kill it before it's born.
우린 그것이 생기기 전에
그것을 제거할 수 있어요
You can stop running.
당신은 그걸 막을 수 있죠
Stay in one place.
자리를 잡아요
Fight.
그리고 싸워요
Mom, we've gotta go now!
엄마!
우린 가야해요, 당장!
Mom!
엄마!
Do it!
작동시켜!
정체 예상
도로 공사중
2007년 9월 3일부터
2007년 9월 24일까지
정체 예상
Where are we?
우리가 어디 있는거지?
Same where.
같은 곳에요
Different when.
시기는 다르지만요
도로 공사중
2007년 9월 3일부터
2007년 9월 24일까지
Check this out!
이것 좀 봐!
좋은 날이야, 자기!
Good day, baby! I got something for ya!
자기를 위해
준비한 게 있는데..
So this is where it all starts?
그럼 모든 게 여기서
시작되는 건가?
This is where Skynet begins?
여기가 스카이넷이
시작되는 곳이야?
Somewhere in there.
저기 어디선가..
And nobody knows we're here.
그럼 우리가 여기 있다는 걸
아는 사람은 아무도 없고?
You're safe.
넌 안전해
- No one is ever safe.
- 누구도 결코 안전하지 않아
Come on.
가자
It is said that the death
of any one person
어떤 한 사람의 죽음이
온 세계의 죽음이라고 말한다
is the death of an entire world.
Certainly for parents,
물론 부모들에겐, 자기 아이의 죽음이
대학살보다 못한 건 아니다
the death of a child
is no less than a holocaust.
In the case of my son,
내 아들의 경우에도
이 말은 글자 그대로 맞는 말이다
these words are literally true.
And finally tonight, amateur video
of what we can only assume
마침내 오늘밤, 진짜라고 밖에
보이지 않던 아마추어 동영상이
대학생들의 엉뚱한
장난이었다고 밝혀졌습니다
is a college prank gone wrong
발가벗은 세 사람이 105번 도로를
가로지르면서 큰 혼란을 일으켰는데..
as three streakers cause chaos
trying to cross the 105 freeway.
Honey, did you hear me? We're late.
자기! 내 얘기 들었어?
우리 늦었다구
Yeah,
그래, 들었어
I heard you.
And even though
we've traveled through time,
그리고 우리가 자연의 법칙을
거슬러 시간을 넘나드는
bent the rules of nature,
여행을 하고 있더라도,
그것들은 내 아들을 찾으려 할 것이고
they will keep coming for him.
Keep trying to kill him.
그를 죽이려고 애쓸 것이다
But until that day...
하지만 그 날이 오기까지는..
It's gonna be one hell of a dogfight.
빌어먹을 치열한 싸움이
있을 것이다
제작 : 권성현
(hasasawl@empal.com)
네이트 드라마 24 자유제작
(http://club.nate.com/24)
조건부배포/수정금지
배포시 제작자와 출처를 꼭 표기해 주세요